(Raj:)What?
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry, Raj.
(Raj:)Why can't I find someone?
(Raj:)I'm smart, I've got a cool job
and my naturally bronzed complexion...
(Raj:)...means I can pull off mustard yellow
in a way most guys can't.
- Aw, honey, it's not you, it's them.
- No, it's not. She was too beautiful for me.
- Why would you say that?
- It's true.
(Raj:)I'm always attracted to women I can't have.
I do it all the time.
(Raj:)I did the same thing with the two of you.
(Amy:)The two of them? I don't understand.
(Raj:)Well, uh, there was a time
when I had a thing for Penny.
(Raj:)I thought she was into me too.
She got drunk and naked...
(Raj:)...and climbed into bed with me.
But apparently, I misread those signals.
(Amy:)And you liked Bernadette also?
(Raj:)That was before Penny.
(Raj:)I make it a rule to only fall for
one of my friends' girlfriends at a time.
(Raj:)I'm very old-fashioned that way.
(Amy:)So at, uh, some point,
you probably had a thing for me too.